{
    "Act1Questions": [
        {
            "question" : "What does Duncan call Macbeth when he hears that Macbeth has defeated Macdonwald?",
            "answers" : ["A traitor", "A coward", "A fine worrior", "A worthy gentleman"],
            "correct" : "A worthy gentleman"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Who is sentenced to death?",
            "answers" : ["Macbeth", "The Thane of Cawdor", "Ross", "Thane of Glamis"],
            "correct" : "The Thane of Cawdor"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What title is given to Macbeth for his bravery in battle?",
            "answers" : ["Becoming thane of Cawdor", "Becoming thane of Glamis", "Becoming thane of Ross", "Becoming thane of Fife"],
            "correct" : "Thane of Cawdor"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What do the witches predict in Act 1, Scene 3 for Macbeth?",
            "answers" : ["He will be king", "He will be tried for treason", "He will have many sons", "He will be a great warrior"],
            "correct" : "He will be king"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Who will be the new Thane of Cawdor?",
            "answers" : ["Macbeth", "Ross", "Malcolm", "Banquo"],
            "correct" : "Macbeth"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What do the witches predict in Act 1, Scene 3 for Banquo?",
            "answers" : ["He will be king", "His children will be kings", "He'll be the new Thane of Cawdor", "He will be a great warrior"],
            "correct" : "His children will be kings"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Who is named as the Prince of Cumberland, the king's heir?",
            "answers" : ["Macbeth", "Malcolm", "Banquo", "Ross"],
            "correct" : "Malcolm"
        },{
            "question":"Who creates the plan to kill King Duncan?",
            "answers":["Macbeth","Malcolm","Lady Macbeth","Duncan"],
            "correct":"Lady Macbeth"
        },
        {
            "question":"Who is planed to take the blame for killing Duncan?",
            "answers":["Banquo", "Macbeth","Lady Macbeth", "The Chamber Maids"],
            "correct":"The Chamber Maids"
        },
        {
            "question":"How does Macbeth reacte to the witches' prophecies?",
            "answers":["He is ecstatic about it", "He is frightened by it", "He is absorbed by the idea", "He disapointed by the grim news"],
            "correct":"The Chamber Maids"
        }

    ]
}